Taco Tuesday on the Amanda Seale Show, and today, unfortunately, is the last day of Black History Month.
But we celebrate Black History Month 365, 366 on a leaping around here at the Amanda Seale Show.
And today, we're about to do another segment called They Did That, highlighting Black inventors.
And this is somebody that I ain't had no idea about this, Amanda.
Who are we talking about today?
William H. Richardson.
Okay, thanks to Black inventor William H. Richardson,
he made a huge improvement to the baby carriage that would make children more amenable to sleeping in the carriage.
You see, he decided to create the stroller so that it could be shaped more like a symmetrical basket than a shell.
And this new design made it easier for parents and nannies to move it around 360 degrees compared to only 90 degrees.
And the biggest part of Richardson's change to the baby carriage was that it was also reversible.
So it made it possible to have anyone pushing the baby face them instead of facing in the opposite direction.
Because of this man, baby carriages and strollers became, one, more affordable and in turn gave middle-class families the ability to buy them during the 1900s.
And two, it allowed for babies to be more comfortable in their actual carriage.
So the next time you're taking the baby out for a stroll in the park, on the streets,
next time someone is helping you carry that stroller up the steps in the subway,
it might be best to keep inventor William H. Richardson in mind.